i'd have
to wait for
i don't call
home
the owner was there that giving him that's him
whatsoever about
some of the
union
recently
we're
going to be
on
the
world
so
the idea
of
the
one
life
vests of him and
his
pat pat
officials are folks like
that
to yourself and
i'll leave so
found
mind you know we made a lot of people's
from
those two days he discussed
with the
transfer
from what is
that the
but if that
white house
press secretary under president so but smith and if
you should not recuse yourself
and how
best to that
and up
i didn't fare
on
why
now
all
of them
to
this move
seven
vida
ow
we'll live
with aidid
no no the rules
of ethics rules are
most people go
all
came down when you evaluate the moves
of
the allied
then
on
i am
a feisty that the law of investigated him
and i have
one more
question river at that
two questions upon
what
you were already considering recusal portland is the first few seconds
to answer and
senator frank it's a question
for you does not thinking of the meeting
with russian ambassador would you do not consider a row of
i was
home
taken aback
all of that that is brand new information
this allegation that
started tonight
involves are
far
they've been making continuous live
with rice and
officials
are
saying that
and for that
struck me the coordinates the
focus
is
and now
live rats effective
positive
slowed down and said
what i did the
one russian official
without without that would be in bath thank you all
right here
the
new
group of of
an el al's minority leader named tupelo see in an interview with politico this morning
calling attorney general sessions recusal an admission that something is wrong
here
are
j.
fuck
are a happy for an
i. m.
palmer and assigned quarter j. chairman at the ice so much for coming
out this morning at the u. over all the more tuning in on line stream we are to be sighted